<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<html><body>
    <p>To successfully connect to PiPedal, one of the following conditions must be true:</p>
    <xul>
        <xli><p>Your Android device and your Raspberry Pi must be connected to the same network using the same Wi-Fi router.</p></xli>
        <xli><p>Your Android device and your Raspberry Pi must be connected to the same network via a PiPedal <i>Auto-Hotpost</i>.</p></xli>
    </xul>
    <p>
        If you are connecting to a PiPedal <i>Auto-Hotspot</i> for the first time, you must connect to the
        Wi-Fi hotspot using the Android Wi-Fi network user interface. Click on <b><i>Connect to Wi-Fi network</i></b> and
        select the PiPedal Wi-Fi hotspot from there.</p>
    <p>The way the <i>PiPedal auto-hotspot</i> feature is intended to work is that:</p>
    <xul>
        <xli><p>When you are at home, your Android device and your Raspberry Pi will connect to each other using your home Wi-Fi router.</p></xli>
        <xli><p>When you are playing away from home, your Raspberry Pi will not be able to find your home Wi-Fi router, so it will automatically start
            a Wi-Fi hotspot. Your Android device also won&#8217;t be able to find your home
            Wi-Fi router, but will find the Wi-Fi hotspot on the Raspberry Pi, and will connect to it automatically, because it remembers it.</p></xli>
    </xul>
    <p>Either way, your Android device connects to a Wi-Fi network that the Raspberry Pi is using, and the PiPedal client automatically discovers and connects to the Raspberry Pi.
     </p>
    <p>
    To get this to work, you will have to configure PiPedal to start up a hotspot network. The PiPedal&#8217;s <i>Auto-Hotspot</i> connection is not enabled by default. Consult PiPedal&#8217;s <a href="https://rerdavies.github.io/pipedal/Configuring.html">online documentation</a> for
        a discussion of how to properly configure Pipedal&#8217;s Auto-Hotspot.
    </p>
    <p>
    You should configure the PiPedal Auto-Hotspot now, so that, when you do take PiPedal out on an adventure away from home, you will be able to connect.
        When you are away from home, you may not have the tools, and the Wi-Fi router
    you need to change PiPedal&#8217;s configuration on your Raspberry Pi. So, do it now, and test that it works before you try to use PiPedal outside of your home.
    If you have multiple PiPedal devices, you can switch connections from the PiPedal user-interface by selecting <b><i>Connect to a different device</i></b> from the PiPedal&#8217;s <b><i>Settings</i></b> panel.
    </p>
    <p>Troubleshooting checklist:</p>
    <xul>
        <xli><p>Have you configured the Pipedal <i>Auto-Hotspot</i>? If not, go to PiPedal&#8217;s <b><i>Settings</i></b> panel, and
        select <b><i>Wi-Fi auto-hotspot</i></b>.</p></xli>
        <xli><p>Have you connected at least once to the Pipedal <i>Auto-Hotspot</i>? If not, tap <b><i>Connect to Wi-Fi network</i></b>.</p></xli>
        <xli><p>If you are at home, are your Android device and your Raspberry Pi both connected to the same Wi-Fi router?</p></xli>
    </xul>
</body></html>
